{
    "id": "5e5c08afb5e246028e547c8382c9cdda",
    "title": "Dare As An Ordinary Verb And An Auxiliary Verb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is a woman who ……………….. what she thinks.",
            "description": "First and fourth options are possible here. When dare is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "dares to say",
                "dares say",
                "dare to say",
                "dare say"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "d41b3c1c1e06459387ba5c42293007e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t .....................… the truth.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary verb, questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "dare to tell",
                "dare tell",
                "dared tell"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5fba272a0c834961b3343c75fb5a1d43"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ………………….. what you think?",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary verb, questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "dare say",
                "dare to say",
                "dares to say"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d77097093014456ca4c814ef0183fd46"
        },
        {
            "question": "I daren’t ………………… what I think.",
            "description": "When dare is used an auxiliary verb, it is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "say",
                "to say"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "930c22128b8247c39b8cc01e960be788"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… out at night.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to. When it is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "dare not go",
                "does not dare to go",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b79c502a4b5344419a46d1ad79c9994a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... the truth.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to. When it is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't dare speak",
                "doesn't dare to speak",
                "daren't to speak"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "602e63e0f98f4618b33d416d4e7ce43d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man didn’t ………………….. the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dare open",
                "dare to open",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "321f8bafc5e54604984b0ff31c45f53c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................... at her face.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to. When it is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to and questions and negatives are made with do.",
            "answers": [
                "don't dare to look",
                "daren't look",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "00a2439da4574962b0313fbbcb971f47"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you dare ………………….. your limits?",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to. When it is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to and questions and negatives are made with do.",
            "answers": [
                "test",
                "to test",
                "to testing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71cf6f1d8043421abdd0ab50c65053e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t ……………….. her eyes.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an auxiliary, it is followed by an infinitive without to. When it is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to and questions and negatives are made with do.",
            "answers": [
                "dare open",
                "dare to open",
                "dared to open"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84c524d7bd5748deb30842b980add625"
        },
        {
            "question": "I dare you ……………… across the river.",
            "description": "The expression ‘I dare you + infinitive’ is used to challenge one another.",
            "answers": [
                "swim",
                "to swim",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95f4e4fc26a0478a804e295fcb2b730f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She dared me ………………. the truth.",
            "description": "The expression ‘I dare you + infinitive’ is used to challenge one another.",
            "answers": [
                "tell",
                "to tell"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4415ed6427e4ad7b63300476d203e6a"
        }
    ]
}